She's having my baby,
and she's not here yet.
-Has her water broken yet?
-I don't know.
When we talked, she said she'd
already passed the mucous plug.
Do we have to know about that?
What'll you do
when you have a baby?
I'll be in the waiting room,
handing out cigars.
Joey's made arrangements to have
his baby in a movie from the '50s.
She could be giving birth in the cab.
Relax. It's only $2
for the first contraction...
...and then 50 cents for each
additional contraction.
What, it's okay
when Chandler does it?
You have to pick your moments.
Did I miss it?
-She's not here yet.
-What's with the guitar?
We might be here for a while.
Things might get musical.
-Where have you been?
-We stopped at the gift shop.
I got this,
and Susan wanted a Chunky.
You're having a baby.
You don't stop for Chunkies.
I used to have that bumper sticker.
You see what I mean?
The One With the Birth
-"Stopped for a Chunky."
-Let it go, Ross.
I got an extra one.
You want this?
-How's my favorite parenting team?
-Dr. Franzblau.
I understand you're thinking
of having a baby.
I see you're nine months pregnant.
That's a good start.
-How are your contractions?
-I love them.
Each one's like a little party
in my uterus.
-Every 4 minutes, lasting 55 seconds.
-59 seconds. Quartz.
Swiss quartz.
-Am I allowed to drink anything?
-lce chips.
-At the nurse's station.
-I'll get it!
-No, I'll get it.
-No, I'm getting it.
Hi. Thought you might like
some ice chips.
-Thanks.
-And if you need anything else l...
...do not believe we've met.
I'm Rachel Greene.
I'm Carol's ex-husband's
sister's roommate.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Dr. Franzblau.
I'm your roommate's brother's
ex-wife's obstetrician.
Oh, that's funny.
I want a baby.
Not tonight, honey.
I got an early day tomorrow.
-Get up. Let's get some coffee.
-Okay, because we never do that.
Shoot, shoot, shoot.
Or just fall down. That's good too.
Knick fan?
-Oh, boy, do they suck.
-Listen, lady
Look. Look at your man, Ewing.
He couldn't hit water
if he was standing on a boat.
-And who do you like?
-Celtics.
Celtics? They couldn't hit a boat if
Wait....
They suck, all right?
Shut up.
It's a rebuilding year
Let me get the father.
We need a father over here.
There's no father.
-Oh, sorry.
-That's okay. I'm fine.
Okay. Right this way.
All the other pregnant women
seem to be going in here.
They're tiny and chubby
And so sweet to touch
But soon they'll grow up
And resent you so much
Now they're yelling at you
And you don 't know why
And you cry and you cry
And you cry
-Thanks, Ross.
-I'm paying you to stop.
Oh, look, twins.
Hi, guys. Oh, cute.
No fair.
I don't even have one.
How come they get two?
-You'll get one.
-When?
Tell you what. When we're 40,
if neither of us are married...
...what do you say we have one?
Why won't I be married
when I'm 40?
I just meant hypothetically.
Hypothetically, why won't I be
married when I'm 40?
What is it? Is there something
unmarriable about me?
Well?
Dear God!
This parachute is a knapsack.
Look at you, dressy-dress.
Did you go home and change?
It's an important day.
I want to look nice.
Has Dr. Franzblau been by?
I haven't seen him.
Where is he?
He is supposed to be here.
What if the baby needs him?
What's the deal with you and doctors?
Is your father a doctor?
Yeah. Why?
No reason.
Mom, we've been through this.
No, I am not calling him.
I don't care if it is his kid,
the guy's a jerk.
No, I am not alone.
Joey's here.
What do you mean "Joey who"?
Joey who?
-Tribbiani.
-Joey Tribbiani.
Yes. Okay. Hold on.
She wants to talk to you.
Take the phone.
Yeah, it's me.
No, we're just friends.
Yeah, I'm single.
Twenty-five.
An actor. Hello?
She's not much of a phone person.
So, what's the deal
with this father guy?
If someone was having my baby,
I'd wanna know about it.
Hey, Knick fan, am I interested
in your views on fatherhood? No.
-Maybe I should just go.
-Maybe you should.
Good luck...
...and take care.
The Celtics problem is that
the players run the team.
-That is so not true.
-Oh, it is.
-Breathe.
You're gonna kill me.
-Fifteen more seconds. 1 4, 1 3, 1 2
-Count faster.
It'll be okay. IKeep focusing on Jordy.
He'll be here soon.
-Three. Two. Who the hell is Jordy?
-Your son.
I don't have a son named Jordy.
We all agreed on Jamie.
Jamie was the name
of Susan's first girlfriend...
...so we went back to Jordy.
What do you mean, back to Jordy?
We never landed on Jordy.
We just passed by it during the whole
Jesse-Cody-Dillon fiasco.
Ow! Leg cramp!
-I got it.
-I got it. I'm doing it.
You get to sleep with her.
I get the cramps.
No, you don't.
That is it.
I want both of you out.
-She started it.
-He did.
I'm trying to get
a person out of my body here...
...and you're not making it
any easier! Now go!
-Thanks.
-See what you did?
-Listen
-Out!
Breathe. Breathe.
What is that? Something exploded.
-That's not the baby, is it?
-Her water broke. Calm down.
Water breaking?
What do you mean? What's that?
Breathe. Breathe.
I'm okay. I'm okay.
That's disgusting. I'm okay.
-This is so your fault.
-How is this my fault?
Carol never threw me out
of a room before you.
There's a lot of things
Carol never did before me.
-Are you trying to be clever?
-You're so threatened by me.
Hey. Okay, all right.
That's it. Get in here.
My God, you guys.
I don't believe you.
There are children
coming into the world here...
...and your fighting isn't
the first thing they should hear.
So stop all the yelling!
Just stop it!
Don't make me do this again!
I don't like my voice like this!
Who wants to hear something ironic?
Are they here yet?
Don't worry,
we're gonna find them.
And until we do,
we are all here for you. Okay?
You were telling me
about Paris. It sounds wonderful.
There was this great little
pastry shop right by my hotel
There you go, dear.
-You find them?
-Not in the gift shop or cafeteria....
Where are Phoebe and Joey?
There's something sinister
going on here.
If you find anyone,
or parts of anyone...
...scream. And scream again.
-Help!
-Come on!
-I'm having a baby in there!
-Hello!
Okay, everyone stand back.
Ow.
All right, good thing
we're in a hospital.
Come on, Lydia, you can do it.
Push him out, push him out.
Harder, harder.
Way out.
Let's get that ball and really move.
Let's get
I was just Yeah, okay.
Push, push, push.
What are you gonna do,
suck the door open?
Help! Help!
And they found their bodies
The very next day
The very next
Mom, everything's going fine.
Ross is great.
He's in a whole other place.
No, he's gone.
No, you don't have to fly back.
Really.
What do you mean "This might be your
only chance"? I'm only 26.
I'm not even thinking
about babies yet.
-Where have you been?
-I just had a baby.
Mazel tov.
It could be one hour or three.
But relax.
She's doing great.
So tell me, are you currently
involved with anyone?
Not at the moment, I'm not. Are you?
No, it's hard enough to get women
to go out with me.
Right. Yeah, I've heard that
about cute doctors.
No, really. I suppose it's because
I spend so much time, you know...
...where I do.
I try not to let work
affect my personal life.
But it's hard when, when you do
what I do. It's, like....
Well, for instance,
what do you do?
I'm a waitress.
Aren't there times when you come home
at night and you're, like:
"If I see one more cup of coffee...."
Gotcha.
-I'm gonna check up on your friend.
-That's fine.
-How'd you know I was here?
-Your mom called me.
So is this her?
No, this is a loaner.
Ours is at the shop.
God, I hope she has my brains.
I'm sorry you had to do this
by yourself.
I wasn't by myself. I had a doctor,
a nurse and a helper guy.
-So did you see who won the game?
-The Knicks by 10. They suck.
They're not so bad.
Come on. Come on.
-You're doing it too hard.
-You have to do it hard or else
Damn it. Damn it.
Damn it, damn it.
This is all your fault.
This should be
the greatest day of my life.
My son is being born,
and I should be in there.
Instead, I'm stuck
in a closet with you.
I have been waiting for this
as much as you.
No one's been waiting
for this as much as I have.
You know what's funny?
You go home with the baby.
Where does that leave me?
You're his father.
Who am l? There's Father's Day.
There's Mother's Day.
There's no Lesbian Lover Day.
Every day is Lesbian Lover Day.
This is so great.
Do you wanna explain that?
I mean, when I was growing up,
my dad left...
...and my mother died
and my stepfather went to jail.
I barely had enough pieces
to make one whole parent.
And here's this baby who has
three whole parents...
...who fight over
who gets to love it the most...
...and it's not even born yet.
It's just the luckiest baby
in the whole world.
I'm sorry. You were fighting.
Where are they?
-They'll be here.
-They wouldn't miss this.
Relax. You're only at 9 centimeters,
and the baby's at zero station.
You are really frightening me.
Somebody wanna help me?
Trying to rip out my heart.
That's great.
Anybody seen a nipple?
Ten centimeters.
Here we go.
-Time to start pushing.
-But they're not here yet.
-I can't tell the baby to wait.
-Oh, God.
-Okay, got the vent open.
-Hi, I'm Ben.
I'm hospital worker Ben.
It's Ben to the rescue.
Ben, you ready? Give me your foot.
On three, Ben.
One, two, three.
Come on, Ben.
That's it, Ben.
What do you see?
I see what appears to be
a dark vent.
Wait.
Yes, it is, in fact, a dark vent.
Pheebs, it's open.
It's open.
Wait. You forgot your legs.
-Push. Push.
-We're here. We're here.
Where have you been?
Long story.
I need you to keep pushing.
I need Excuse me, can I have this?
There's too many people here.
There's about to be one more.
So if you're not an ex-husband or
lesbian life partner, out you go.
-Bye-bye.
-Good luck, you guys.
Do you have to be
Carol's lesbian life partner?
Out.
Here he comes.
Let me see. I've gotta see.
A head.
It's huge.
How are you doing this?
You're not helping.
You're doing great.
-Hello?
-Oh, sorry.
What do you see?
We got a head. We got arms.
Oh, look at the little fingers.
A chest and a stomach...
...and it's a boy, definitely a boy.
Legs, knees and feet.
He's here.
He's a person.
-Look.
-What does he look like?
IKind of like my Uncle Ed,
covered in Jell-O.
Really?
You guys, he's beautiful.
Thanks, Pheebs.
No shouting, but we still need
a name for this little guy.
-How about Ben?
-I like Ben.
Ben.
Ben's good. How come you never
mentioned Ben before?
We just cooked it up.
That's what we were off doing.
-Can we come in?
-Yeah, come on.
I know. I know.
Everybody, there's someone
I'd like you to meet.
-This is Ben.
-Hi, Ben.
Ben, this is everybody.
Susan, he looks just like you.
Thanks.
I can't believe one of us
actually has one of these.
I know.
I still am one of these.
Can l?
Okay, the head. You gotta....
I'm your Aunt Monica.
Yes, I am.
I will always have gum.
Ben...
... I want you to know that
there may be some times when...
... I may not be around like this.
But I'll still always come back...
...Iike this.
And sometimes,
I may be away longer...
...Iike this.
But I'll still always come back...
And sometimes, I'll want you to steal
third and I'll go like this:
He is so amazing.
Yeah, I know. Look at him.
Nothing.
I don't think that's his name.
Look, he's closing his eyes.
Look, he's opening his eyes.
He doesn't do much, does he?
Nope, this is pretty much it.
You guys wanna get some coffee?
I'll see you guys later.
He's closing his eyes again.